{ "results": [
	{
        "answer": "",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "TaYNbb94gI"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-01T04:07:44.801Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "X9xl0J2TSq"
        },
        "objectId": "pzqTYwzXKp",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "B2XqSdjVTN"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-03T19:15:41.662Z"
    },
	{
        "accepted": true,
        "answer": "",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "KuF4e336N3"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-03T19:45:31.420Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "X9xl0J2TSq"
        },
        "objectId": "MOaqvl8Fzb",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "B2XqSdjVTN"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-03T20:02:41.723Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "Hi ",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "5mg8bgqmuQ"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-03T22:48:21.849Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "B2XqSdjVTN"
        },
        "objectId": "8UBDeppZbF",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "X9xl0J2TSq"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-06T03:25:14.205Z"
    },
	{
        "accepted": true,
        "answer": "Hhg",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "3vx7JkG0Dc"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-10T02:25:44.548Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "B2XqSdjVTN"
        },
        "objectId": "SKjnKEg92Z",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "X9xl0J2TSq"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-10T02:34:48.958Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "dLrkoFGM7G"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-10T23:12:01.577Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "X9xl0J2TSq"
        },
        "objectId": "5dYFqt6cdv",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "B2XqSdjVTN"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-11T03:33:14.506Z"
    },
	{
        "accepted": true,
        "answer": "Items I\n",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "ontUmkPBse"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-11T01:31:14.942Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "B2XqSdjVTN"
        },
        "objectId": "XeWxi1ZyGD",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "X9xl0J2TSq"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-11T01:31:46.298Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "NV8zkKfvOo"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-17T04:44:22.309Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "rDbI0NqhlC"
        },
        "objectId": "HufItAdgBf",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "B2XqSdjVTN"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-24T16:29:10.536Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "09Cg7kl4lq"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-20T18:10:10.968Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "X9xl0J2TSq"
        },
        "objectId": "06D3oIQ43z",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "B2XqSdjVTN"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-23T21:50:06.793Z"
    },
	{
        "accepted": true,
        "answer": "",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "P0pTib1etG"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-20T18:11:08.724Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "X9xl0J2TSq"
        },
        "objectId": "B4BCa4sag6",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "rDbI0NqhlC"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-20T18:21:30.156Z"
    },
	{
        "accepted": true,
        "answer": "It doggy",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "shJYUrRdEO"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-23T23:08:42.153Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "67Cg288t5f"
        },
        "objectId": "82Uxg1vGLJ",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "jy5KMXp4xu"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-23T23:11:44.111Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "ArmWMkl3wh"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-24T16:29:41.376Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "67Cg288t5f"
        },
        "objectId": "RCqOp3vO5n",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "B2XqSdjVTN"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-24T16:29:43.374Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "Shaggys angel ",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "E8AXeJohC3"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-25T15:16:29.780Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "6G37V4PSJE"
        },
        "objectId": "eMUmVSbr3s",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "TjJYRmvTUo"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-25T15:33:21.022Z"
    },
	{
        "accepted": true,
        "answer": "",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "5RUHVU6Uv2"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-30T20:43:13.520Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "VwV4pFuUoG"
        },
        "objectId": "hSZzqnDc9n",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "TjJYRmvTUo"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-10-30T20:43:59.899Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "Bugsy B, cause my eyes ðŸ˜³",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "9UxNLCliXo"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-30T20:44:43.426Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "VwV4pFuUoG"
        },
        "objectId": "YbHNuU6xtA",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "VEYC1cjgut"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-11-07T21:31:02.972Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "Swift a",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "AFgbQwOSUq"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-10-30T23:01:32.238Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "VwV4pFuUoG"
        },
        "objectId": "d6YXF1jzlx",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "GgvAiH7AXZ"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-11-07T18:55:28.163Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "Byv8fILWW1"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-11-01T14:25:14.765Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "VwV4pFuUoG"
        },
        "objectId": "fxoWnfOYgQ",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "QnRr5Kq4wu"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-11-07T21:31:09.996Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "Baha'is",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "n0LDDpDR13"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-11-01T16:55:54.643Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "VwV4pFuUoG"
        },
        "objectId": "2m8uRYvEYj",
        "questionText": "If you were a rapper, what would your stage name be?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "VEYC1cjgut"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-11-07T21:31:11.227Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "Ew",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "9Se6Uasxda"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-11-07T18:51:01.293Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "GgvAiH7AXZ"
        },
        "objectId": "s2g2VuVh5D",
        "questionText": "Is lactating chocolate milk something that peaks your interest?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "GGB6cTTOYJ"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-11-07T18:55:07.193Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "The only thing that would have to go back and I don't think that I have ",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "5AmAHYYscy"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-11-07T18:56:00.791Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "GgvAiH7AXZ"
        },
        "objectId": "A16lVNSryg",
        "questionText": "Favorite Nickelodeon show from the 90â€™s and why in one sentence?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "GGB6cTTOYJ"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-11-16T03:17:07.832Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "Hfhhj",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "fsF6uTsXxx"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-11-09T17:55:43.893Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "GgvAiH7AXZ"
        },
        "objectId": "HNIG6ZXimZ",
        "questionText": "You're reincarnated as __________?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "GGB6cTTOYJ"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-11-09T17:55:44.458Z"
    },
	{
        "answer": "yrdjfghk",
        "chat": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "Chat",
            "objectId": "EzLRWAiLBO"
        },
        "createdAt": "2014-11-16T23:40:53.920Z",
        "fromUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "GGB6cTTOYJ"
        },
        "objectId": "aI9nJDZmea",
        "questionText": "A wizard shows up, gives you their wand. What do you do?",
        "toUser": {
            "__type": "Pointer",
            "className": "_User",
            "objectId": "7qDFZeIBcf"
        },
        "updatedAt": "2014-11-16T23:40:54.494Z"
    }
] }